=My Fairy Doctor= =Episode 32=
= My Fairy Doctor = = الحلقة 32 =
Sorry, Qizi.
آسف يا قيزي.
Why don't you return to the painting?
لماذا لا تعود إلى اللوحة؟
I can just look at your portrait.
يمكنني فقط إلقاء نظرة على صورتك.
That's impossible.
هذا مستحيل.
I had only one chance.
لم يكن لدي سوى فرصة واحدة.
Then why did you come out again?
إذن لماذا خرجت مرة أخرى؟
Because I haven't properly bid you farewell.
لأنني لم أودعك بشكل صحيح.
Then
ثم
can we reconnect?
هل يمكننا إعادة الاتصال؟
Let's just enjoy our last moments.
دعنا فقط نستمتع بلحظاتنا الأخيرة.
Okay.
تمام.
I'll do it for you.
سوف افعلها من اجلك.
Yide.
ييد.
Yes?
نعم؟
I want to marry Qizi.
أريد الزواج من قيزي.
Father.
أب.
If you don't agree, I will...
إذا كنت لا توافق ، فسأفعل ...
What?
ماذا؟
Qinjian.
كينجين.
Do you really love my daughter?
هل حقا تحب ابنتي؟
Yes.
نعم.
Father.
أب.
Is that a yes?
هل هذه نعم؟
I can't say no
لا استطيع ان اقول لا
because you two have already...
لأنكما بالفعل ...
Father.
أب.
You are the best.
أنت الأفضل.
When did you become so open-minded?
متى أصبحت منفتح الذهن؟
This is not like you.
هذا ليس مثلك
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I've always been keen on Qinjian.
لطالما كنت حريصًا على Qinjian.
If Wen Nianzhou
إذا ون Nianzhou
hadn't said that Tang Qinjian was our ancestor,
لم يقل أن تانغ كينجيان كان سلفنا ،
they would have
سيكون لديهم
gotten married a long time ago.
تزوجت منذ وقت طويل.
Caichen.
كايشن.
Are you really not our ancestor?
هل أنت حقا لست أسلافنا؟
I think you should really eat more
أعتقد أنك يجب أن تأكل أكثر حقًا
fish to nourish your brain.
الأسماك لتغذية عقلك.
So I was kept in the dark.
لذلك ظللت في الظلام.
(From now on,)
(من الان فصاعدا،)
(you must never leave my side.)
(يجب ألا تترك جانبي أبدًا).
(Since the bracelet has chosen you,)
(منذ أن اختارك السوار ،)
(I hope you will tell your parents)
(أتمنى أن تخبر والديك)
(that you will marry me soon.)
(أنك ستتزوجني قريبًا.)
(You are my wife)
(أنت زوجتي)
(and I am your husband.)
(وأنا زوجك).
(Remember.)
(تذكر.)
(Call me the Divine Physician.)
(اتصل بي بالطبيب الإلهي.)
Tang Caichen.
تانغ كايتشن.
Don't think I'm yours just because
لا أعتقد أنني ملكك لمجرد
we sleep in the same room.
ننام في نفس الغرفة.
I hate you.
أكرهك.
Keep your distance from me.
حافظ على بعدك عني.
Bow to Heaven and Earth.
تنحني للسماء والأرض.
Bow to parents.
انحن للوالدين.
Bow to each other.
تنحني لبعضهم البعض.
To the bridal bedroom.
إلى غرفة نوم الزفاف.
Wait.
انتظر.
♪Light up all the stars♪
♪ تضيء كل النجوم
♪Wish for staying with you forever♪
♪ أتمنى البقاء معك إلى الأبد
♪You're like the thriving Tang dynasty♪
♪ أنت مثل سلالة تانغ المزدهرة ♪
♪No matter if we're fated or not♪
♪ لا يهم إذا كنا قدّرنا أم لا
♪We still love each other♪
♪ ما زلنا نحب بعضنا البعض